Finding Aid for Richard C. Frank papers, 1958-2004
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Project Files
  - Detroit Office
    - Charles Lange Freer House, Detroit
      - Project Files 1993-1994, 8 folders (Box 25)
    - Fulton Steam Facility, Grand Rapids 1997-1998 (Box 25)
    - Garfield Building, Detroit 1995 (Box 25)
    - William F. Goodyear Building, Offering Memorandum for Purchase and Renovation, Ann Arbor 1983 (Box 25)
    - John N. Gott House, Ann Arbor 1980 (Box 25)
    - Grand Haven Historical Survey 1982 (Box 25)
    - Grand Rapids Central City Historical Survey 1980 (Box 25)
    - Grand Rapids Public Library, West Side Branch
      - "Building Envelope Investigation and Cost Estimates," 1995 (Box 26)
      - Project Files 1995-1996, 6 folders (Box 26)
      - Architectural Drawings, blue line prints, includes copies of original plan (Tube 75)
      - Architectural Drawings, blue line prints, includes copies of original plan (Tube 76)
    - Grand Traverse Medical Campus, Traverse City
      - Grand Traverse Commons Development, Request for Proposal 1995 (Box 26)
      - "Through the Years: A Brief Look at Traverse City State Hospital," undated (Box 26)
    - Project Files 1995-1998, 17 folders (Box 26)
    - Grand Trunk Union Depot, Rehabilitation Study, Duran 1980 (Box 26)
    - Greer School, Plymouth/Canton 1996 (Box 26)
    - Grosse Point Farms
      - Project File 1987-1992 (Box 26)
      - "History of Grosse Point Farms to 1940" 1988 (Box 26)
      - Final Report 1989 (Box 26)
    - Gun Lake Restaurant 1980 (Box 27)
    - Hartwick Pines, Memorial Building Restoration, Architectural Drawings (Tube 77)
    - Historic Preservation Inventory, Grand Rapids 1973 (Box 27)
    - Kellogg Residence, Battle Creek 1989-1990 (Box 27)
    - Kingsmill Plantation, Williamsburg, Virginia
      - A Preservation Study 1985 (Box 27)
      - Project Files 1984-1985, 5 folders (Box 27)
    - Lake Erie Gateway, Development Plan, Monroe 1980 (Box 27)
    - Lansing Women's Club House, A Study of Restoration and Renewed Use 1976 (Box 27)
    - Leslie Downtown 1994 (Box 27)
    - Library of Congress, Historic Preservation Specifications, Washington, D.C. undated (Box 27)
    - Mackinac Island State Park Commission, Historic Preservation Planning...a regional study 1972 (Box 27)
    - Mackinac Island State Park, Major Special Maintenance and Remodeling
      - Project Manual, Package 2: arch Rock 1998 (Box 27)
      - Package 1: Fort Mackinac Stone Walls 1998 (Box 27)
      - Preliminary Design Report 1998 (Box 27)
      - Project Files 1998, 5 folders (Box 27)
      - Project Files 1998, 2 folders (Box 28)
      - Hawkins Residence, East Bluff 1994 (Box 28)
      - Architectural Drawings, blue line prints (Tube 78)
    - Mainstreet Holland Building Improvement, Holland 1994 (Box 28)
    - Manistee Downtown, Preservation and Development Plan 1981 (Box 28)
    - Marshall Hall and Old Botany Hall, Michigan State University 1998, 4 folders (Box 28)
    - McAuley Building, Saint Mary's Mercy Medical Center, Grand Rapids 1999-2000 (Box 28)
    - Merchant's Row, Detroit 2002 (Box 28)
    - Metro Airport, Wayne County 1994 (Box 28)
    - Metzger Realty, East Lansing 1997, 2 folders (Box 28)
    - Michigan Farm Bureau, An Expansion Study, Lansing 1967 (Box 28)
    - Michigan Theater, Ann Arbor
      - Phase III, Restoration and Rehabilitation 1997 (Box 28)
      - Project Files 1980-1984, 1995-1997, 6 folders (Box 28)
      - Project Files 1980-1984, 1995-1997, 12 folders (Box 29)
      - Architectural Drawings, original plan copies (Tube 79)
      - Architectural Drawings, blue line prints (Tube 80)
      - Architectural Drawings, blue line prints (Tube 81)
      - Architectural Drawings, blue line prints (Tube 82)
      - Architectural Drawings, blue line prints (Tube 83)
    - Michilimackinac State Park, General Development Plan 1968 (Box 29)
    - Millwright's House and Forge, Mill Creek State Historic Park
      - Reconstruction Concepts 1993-1994 (Box 29)
      - Project Files 1992-1994, 6 folders (Box 29)
      - Architectural Drawings (Tube 84)
      - Architectural Drawings (Tube 85)
    - Monroe, Downtown Façade Study 1981 (Box 29)
    - Moross House, Detroit undated (Box 29)
    - Charles Stewart Mott Foundation Headquarters, Flint
      - Qualifications for Planning and Design Services 1999 (Box 29)
      - A Preliminary Space Program Study for New Headquarters Facilities 2000 (Box 30)
      - A Preliminary Space Program Study For New Headquarters Facilities 2002 (Box 30)
    - Music Hall Center for Performing Arts, Saline 1991-1992 (Box 30)
    - New Haven Depot 1994-1996, 3 folders (Box 30)
    - Old Post Office, Ann Arbor, Schematic Design Study 1978 (Box 30)
    - Old South Channel Lights, St. Clair County
      - Proposal for A/E Services for South Channel Front and Rear Range Lights Restoration Work 2004 (Box 30)
      - Restoration Master Plan 2002 (Box 30)
      - Reconstruction Master Plan 2002 (Box 30)
      - Project Files 2001-2002, 3 volumes; 5 folders (Box 30)
    - Palmer/Ryan House, Ann Arbor
      - A Master Plan Study 1980 (Box 30)
    - Phoenix Furniture Company Building, Grand Rapids 1988, 3 folders (Box 30)
    - Piquette Plant Preservation Project 1998
      - Project Files 1998, 14 folders (Box 31)
      - Presentation Notebook 1999 (Box 31)
    - Plymouth
      - A Proposal to Undertake a Downtown Historic District Study 1993 (Box 31)
    - Preservation Urban Design Incorporated
      - Planning Services: Surveys, Downtown Studies, and Neighborhood Studies 1982 (Box 31)
    - Rochester Golf and Country Club 1997 (Box 31)
    - Sault Ste. Marie, A Report on a Proposed Development 1967 (Box 31)
    - Schoolcraft House, A Feasibility Study, Sault Ste. Marie 1976 (Box 31)
    - Schostak Development, Merchant's Row, Detroit 1999-2001, 2 folders (Box 31)
    - Sibley House, A Restorative Maintenance Master Plan, Detroit
      - 1977 (Box 31)
    - Smithsonian Institution Arts and Industries Building
      - Roof and Façade Restoration 1980 (Box 31)
      - Architectural Drawings Booklet 1980 (Box 31)
      - Structural Condition Report, Range Roofs and Tower Spires 1980 (Box 31)
    - Specification Master Project Notebook 1975-1998, 3 folders (Box 31)
    - Specification Master Project Notebook 1975-1998, 3 folders (Box 32)
    - St. Mary's Church, Architectural Survey/Analysis, Detroit
      - 1981 (Box 32)
    - Ste. Anne de Michilimackinac, Scrapbook 1973 (Box 32)
    - Stanley Residence, Ann Arbor
      - Project File 1997 (Box 32)
      - Architectural Drawings, original pencil and ink drawings (Tube 86)
    - Starr House, Restoration Plan, Royal Oak (Box 32)
    - State Theater, Ann Arbor 1998, 2 folders (Box 32)
    - Stuart Neighborhood, Kalamazoo 1993-1994 (Box 32)
    - Thompson Farm House, Southfield 1998 (Box 32)
    - Towner House, Ypsilanti 1993, 2 folders (Box 32)
    - Tuomy House, Ann Arbor, Rehabilitation Report 1984 (Box 32)
    - Turner-Dodge House, Lansing
      - Summary, Preservation Master Plan 1993 (Box 32)
      - Appendix, Preservation Master Plan 1993 (Box 32)
      - Summary Preservation Master Plan 1993 (Box 32)
      - Request for Qualifications 1993 (Box 32)
      - Report undated (Box 32)
      - Christman Construction Proposal 1993 (Box 32)
      - Construction management Report 1995 (Box 32)
      - Project Files 1994, 3 folders (Box 32)
      - Project Files 1994, 23 folders (Box 33)
    - Village Green of Southfield 1985 (Box 33)
    - Voigt house, Grand Rapids Public Museum 1988-1990, 4 folders (Box 33)
    - Westside Neighborhood Plan, Ann Arbor 1977 (Box 33)
    - Ypsilanti District Library 1998 (Box 33)
    - Ypsilanti Downtown Façade Improvement Plan 1980 (Box 33)
- Orchestra Hall 1965-1999
  The Orchestra Hall, 1965-1999 series (4.5 feet, 4 tubes) documents three decades of renovations to the historic Orchestra Hall of Detroit. The project files reflect every phase of the building's preservation, from the schematic design phase to the construction documents and bidding phase. The project files also contains correspondence related to project grants, construction management and contract negotiations. Unlike the Orchestra Hall paper records, which illustrate the span of the project over many years, the architectural drawings primarily reflect the later phases of the Orchestra Hall restoration.
  - Architectural Drawings
    - Orchestra Hall IV-V, blue line prints (Tube 87)
    - Orchestra Hall VI-VII, blue line prints (Tube 88)
    - Floor Plans, original pencil and ink on mylar (Tube 89)
    - Longitudinal Section, Winch Schedule and Floor plan copies, blue line prints (Tube 90)
  - Project Notebook 1972-1973 (Box 34)
  - Project Notebook 1973-1976 (Box 34)
  - Minutes and Authorizations Notebook 1978-1979 (Box 34)
  - Contract File 1973-1976 (Box 34)
  - Orchestra Hall 1974-1977 (Box 34)
  - Smith, Hinchman & Grylls Associates (File No. 10987) 1965-1973 (Box 34)
  - 1208
    - 101: Master File 1978 (Box 34)
    - 101: Correspondence File 1979-1981, 2 folders (Box 34)
    - 101: Properties Committee Minutes 1978-1980, 2 folders (Box 34)
    - 102: Plaster Side Walls 1978, 2 folders (Box 34)
    - 103: State Electrical, Master File 1978 (Box 34)
    - 104: Oval Lobby, Correspondence File 1978 (Box 34)
    - 105: Electrical Safety 1978 (Box 34)
    - 108: Completion Report 1980 (Box 34)
    - 109: Main Floor Seating, Master File 1979 (Box 34)
    - 110: Seating Phase II 1980 (Box 34)
    - 111: Mezzanine Ladies Lounge, Correspondence File 1980 (Box 34)
    - 111: Mezzanine Ladies Lounge, Project Notebook 1980 (Box 34)
  - Historical Information 1971-1976 (Box 34)
  - Orchestral Hall Site 1979 (Box 34)
  - Historical Designation Board 1980-1981 (Box 34)
  - Codes 1971-1981 (Box 34)
  - 1250 Balcony Restoration 1980-1981
    - Master File 1980 (Box 35)
    - Correspondence File 1980 (Box 35)
    - Construction Administration 1980 (Box 35)
    - Electrical Specs. 1980 (Box 35)
    - Field Set Notebook 1980 (Box 35)
  - 1208-1250-1259 Correspondence relating to grants 1979-1981 (Box 35)
  - 1259 Master Plan Update 1980-1982, 2 folders (Box 35)
  - Dead File 1978 (Box 35)
  - 1333 Balcony Restoration Phase II 1981-1982
    - 105: Northeast stair and door, Master Spec 1981 (Box 35)
    - 107: Promenade and Restrooms, Master Spec 1981 (Box 35)
    - 108: Railings and Plaster, Master Spec 1978-1981, 2 folders (Box 35)
    - 109: Ticket Lobby, Master Spec 1981 (Box 35)
    - 110: Fire Protection II, Master Spec 1981 (Box 35)
    - 110: Fire Protection System Notebook 1981 (Box 35)
    - 111: Oval Lobby and Stair, Master Spec 1981 (Box 35)
  - Project Notebook 1978-1979, 2 folders (Box 36)
  - Project Completion Report 1980 (Box 36)
  - Master Plan for the Preservation of Orchestra Hall, Phase I Supplement 1981 (Box 36)
  - 19333-113: Re-roofing 1982, 2 folders (Box 36)
  - Life Safety Master Plan 1981 (Box 36)
  - 19367.00: Stage Ventilation 1980-1983, 2 folders (Box 36)
  - 19367.01: Stage Ventilation 1983 (Box 36)
  - 19406.00: Traffic and Parking Study, Correspondence 1983-1984 (Box 36)
  - 19406.00: Traffic and Parking Study 1984 (Box 36)
  - Negatives undated (Box 36)
  - Kresge Foundation Correspondence 1980 (Box 36)
  - Exterior Stairways 1980-1981 (Box 36)
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes 1985 (Box 36)
  - Completion Report 1986 (Box 36)
  - Program Analysis 1987 (Box 36)
  - Master Plan 1987 (Box 36)
  - Master Design Plan 1987 (Box 36)
  - News Releases 1987 (Box 36)
  - Orchestra Hall III
    - 19412.00: Correspondence 1984-1985, 2 folders (Box 36)
    - 19412.01: Exterior Stabilization 1984-1986 (Box 36)
    - 19412.01: Exterior Spec. 1984 (Box 36)
    - 19412.01: Lax Construction. 1984-1986 (Box 36)
    - 19412.02: Stage Main Drape, Correspondence 1984 (Box 36)
    - 19412.03: Stage Lifts 1984 (Box 36)
  - Orchestra Hall IV
    - Offices 1985-1986 (Box 36)
    - Controls 1986 (Box 36)
    - Stage Enclosure 1985, 2 folders (Box 36)
    - Structural, Darvas Associates 1984-1985 (Box 36)
    - Schematic 1985, 2 folders (Box 36)
    - Construction Administration 1985-1988 (Box 37)
    - Acoustics 1979-1985 (Box 37)
    - Stage Appearance 1979-1985 (Box 37)
    - HVAC Master Plan 1986 (Box 37)
    - Contract Documents 1985 (Box 37)
    - Addition Presentation 1983 (Box 37)
    - Post Symphony 1987 (Box 37)
  - Orchestra Hall V
    - Gridiron 1983 (Box 37)
    - Grilles 1985-1986 (Box 37)
    - Project Files 1987-1988, 2 folders (Box 37)
  - Greek Room Expansion 1988 (Box 37)
  - General 1985-1989, 2 folders (Box 37)
  - Lawsuit 1987-1990 (Box 37)
  - Orchestra Hall VI 1989 (Box 37)
  - Orchestra Hall VIII
    - Cost and Construction 1990, 2 folders (Box 37)
    - Sound System. 1990 (Box 37)
    - Meeting Notes 1990-1992 (Box 37)
  - Orchestra Hall IX 1991 (Box 37)
  - News Releases 1990 (Box 38)
  - Decorative Paintings 1990-1991 (Box 38)
  - Signage and Plaques 1991 (Box 38)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondences 1991-1992 (Box 38)
    (awards, misc. projects, etc.)
  - Parking Lots 1991-1992 (Box 38)
  - Stage House Roof Deck 1992 (Box 38)
  - Orchestra Hall X 1992 (Box 38)
  - Master Planning Study 1996 (Box 38)
  - General 1997 (Box 38)
  - General 1998 (Box 38)
  - Impact Report 1998 (Box 38)
  - Photographs and Negatives 1998 (Box 38)
  - General 1999 (Box 38)
- Crossroads Village 1975-1979
  The Crossroads Village, 1975-1979 series (5.75 feet, 8 tubes) contains paper records and architectural drawings concerning the Crossroads Village park near Flint, which houses 34 historic structures, including a train depot, cider mill, and a one room schoolhouse.
  - Crossroads Village, Phase 1
    (project no.1101)
    - General Files
      - Contract Documents (Box 9)
      - "Crossroads Village" (Box 9)
      - Genesee County Parks & Recreation Commission, 7 folders (Box 9)
      - Maps (Box 9)
    - Rose Engineering (Box 9)
    - Village Church (Box 9)
    - 109 -- Cider Mill, 3 folders (Box 9)
    - 116 -- Site Work (Box 9)
    - 117 -- Fenton Opera House, 5 folders (Box 9)
    - 117 -- Fenton Opera House (Box 10)
    - 119 -- Saw Mill (Box 10)
    - 120 -- Atlas Grist Mill (Box 10)
    - 124 -- Mill Pond / Raceway (Box 10)
    - 125 -- Village Church, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - 126 -- Vassar Bank, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Cross Roads Village, Phase II
    (project no.1235)
    - General Files, 3 folders (Box 10)
    - 101 -- Genesee County Parks & Recreation Commission, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - 102 -- Atlas Grist Mill II, 3 folders (Box 10)
    - 103 -- Atlas Grist Mill III, 3 folders (Box 10)
    - 104 -- Vassar Bank II, 3 folders (Box 10)
    - 105 -- Fenton Opera House, Colwell Opera House (Box 10)
    - 105 -- Fenton Opera House, Colwell Opera House, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - 106 -- Fenton Opera House Exterior (Box 11)
    - 107 -- New Commercial Building / Manwaring, 4 folders (Box 11)
    - 108 -- Mill Pond, 3 folders (Box 11)
    - 109 -- Landscape Master Plan (Box 11)
    - 110 -- Signage, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - 111 -- Interpretative Master Plan, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - 112 -- GPRC / Barn, 4 folders (Box 11)
    - 113 -- Wood Frame Residence, 4 folders (Box 11)
    - 114 -- Attica Hotel, 3 folders (Box 11)
  - Cross Roads Village, Village Farm (Box 11)
    (project no.1278)
  - Cross Roads Village II, Orientation Center (Box 11)
    (project no.1314)
  - Miscellaneous Project Files and Architectural Drawings
    - Articles and Illustrations (Box 12)
    - Atlas Grist Mill (Box 12)
    - Backhouses Architectural Drawings (Tube 44)
    - Bandshell Architectural Drawings (Tube 45)
    - Barn Architectural Drawings (Tube 46)
    - Barton Garage / Blacksmith Shop (incl. photos, slides) (Box 12)
    - Buzzell House (Box 12)
    - Cider Mill
      - Project Records, 2 folders (Box 12)
      - Architectural Drawings (Tube 45)
    - Clayton Townhall (Box 12)
    - Commercial Building Architectural Drawings (Tube 49)
    - Contractors List (Box 12)
    - Corunna Road Building (Box 12)
    - Davison Depot (Box 12)
    - Doctor's Office
      - Project Files (Box 12)
      - Architectural Drawings (Tube 47)
    - Durant Garage (Box 12)
    - Eldridge House
      - Project Records (Box 12)
      - Architectural Drawings (Tube 47)
    - Fenton Opera House
      - General Files, 2 folders (Box 12)
      - Photographs
        - Queen Esther Play, 1901 (Box 12)
        - Photograph, Clarence Play, by Booth Tarkington, 1922 (Box 12)
        - Photographs; Negatives (Box 12)
      - Preliminary Research (Box 12)
      - Architectural Drawings (Tube 48)
    - Fire Protection (Box 12)
    - Fox House
      - Project Records (Box 12)
      - Architectural Drawings (Tube 47)
    - General 1977 (Box 12)
    - General Files, 4 folders (Box 12)
    - General Files (Box 13)
    - Genesee County Board of Commissioners, Local Public Works Application, Historic Crossroads Village Phase II Development Program (loose item) (Box 13)
    - Genesee Recreation Area, "Historic Crossroads Village" (Box 13)
    - Hotel Architectural Drawings (Tube 50)
    - Interpretation
      - Preface (Box 13)
      - Introduction (Box 13)
      - I. The Historical Setting (Box 13)
      - II. The Role of Authentic Appearances (Box 13)
      - III. The Visitor And The Experience (Box 13)
      - IV. Influences of Interpretation (Box 13)
      - V. Potential Interpretive Themes (Box 13)
      - VI. Recommended Interpretive Techniques (Box 13)
      - General Files, 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Landscaping
      - Project Records (Box 13)
      - Architectural Drawings (Tube 51b)
    - Lawyer's Office Proposed
      - Project Records (Box 13)
      - Architectural Drawings (Tube 46)
    - Mill Pond / Raceway (Box 13)
    - Mott Farm / Village Farm
      - Creating The Crossroads Village Farm (Box 13)
      - General File (Box 13)
      - GCPRC, Genesee County Parks and Recreation Commission (Box 13)
      - Graphics (Box 13)
      - Project Notebook (Box 13)
      - Notes (Box 13)
      - Preliminary Draft (Box 13)
      - Rain Data (Box 13)
      - Research (Box 13)
      - Architectural Drawings (Tube 51a)
    - Original Drawings 1975 (Box 14)
    - Outbuildings (Box 14)
    - Phase I, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Sawmill
      - Project Records (Box 14)
      - Architectural Drawings (Tube 45)
    - School Architectural Drawings (Tube 47)
    - Services (Box 14)
    - Sidewalks, Fences, Lighting, etc. (Box 14)
    - Signage (Box 14)
    - Site Plans Architectural Drawings (Tube 51b)
    - Stanley School (Box 14)
    - Township Hall Architectural Drawings (Tube 47)
    - Vassar Bank
      - Project Records (Box 14)
      - Architectural Drawings (Tube 49)
    - Village Church Architectural Drawings (Tube 46)
    - Water Supply and Sanitary Sewer Specifications (Box 14)
    - Wisner Carriage Barn
      - Project Files (Box 14)
      - Architectural Drawings (Tube 46)
- Smithsonian Institution, Arts and Industries Building 1983
  The Smithsonian Institution, Arts and Industries Building, 1983 series (3 feet, 2 tubes) contains the records of Richard Frank's work on the exterior of this historic structure in Washington, D.C. Forty-eight architectural drawings from this project were preserved in photographic form.
  - Archival Material (Box 14)
  - Construction Administration, 4 folders (Box 14)
  - Correspondence File, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Cost Estimates, 3 folders (Box 15)
  - Doors (Box 15)
  - Exterior Restoration of the Arts and Industries Building
    - Project Files, 1 items; 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Architectural Drawings (Tube 33)
    - Architectural Drawings (Tube 34)
  - General Files, 1 volumes; 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Loose Items (Box 16)
  - Phase I
    - Administrative (Box 16)
    - Correspondence Files, 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Final Report (Box 16)
  - Phase II
    - Administrative (Box 16)
    - Correspondence, 3 folders (Box 16)
    - Exterior Restoration of the Arts and Industries Building (Box 16)
    - General File (Box 16)
  - Phase III Correspondence (Box 16)
  - Photographs
    - "Dead Files" (incl. contact sheets, negatives, and transparencies) (Box 16)
    - Loose Photograph (Box 16)
    - P.U.D.I (Box 16)
    - Photographs of Architectural Drawings, 48 envelopes (Box 17)
  - Preliminary Survey March 1980 (Box 17)
  - Research File (Box 17)
  - Roof and Façade Rehabilitation Preliminary Survey March 1980 (Box 17)
  - Roof and Façade Preliminary Recommendations April 1980 (Box 17)
  - Specifications, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Structural Condition Report May 1980 (Box 17)
- Other Files
  The Other Files series contains office files not related to any specific architectural project. Instead, the material provides a generalized look into Richard Frank's architectural career. The material is arranged in chronological order. Included in the series are notes from Richard Frank's time as a lecturer at Columbia University and the visual aids and sketches from a historic preservation workshop he gave in Monroe, Michigan in 1980. The series also contains correspondence relating to Frank's resignation from Preservation / Urban Design / Incorporated in 1984.
  - Resume and Professional Profile undated (Box 38)
  - Certificates and Awards 1953-1997 (Box 38)
    (see also oversize folder Ac)
  - Richard C. Frank 1958-1974, 1987 (Box 38)
  - Project Master List 1960-1999 (Box 38)
  - Laitala and Nuechterlein Associates 1961 (Box 38)
  - St. Peter's Episcopal Church, Tecumseh, Michigan 1962 (Box 38)
  - 1964 Frank family volume containing inscription from his father (Box 38)
  - Owosso Speech 1967 (Box 38)
  - Bicentennial Committee, Michigan Historical Commission/Historical Society of Michigan 1971-1972 (Box 38)
  - Presentation Notes 1973-1983, 3 folders (Box 38)
  - Richard Frank, Personal 1973 (Box 38)
  - Richard Frank, Personal 1974 (Box 38)
  - Richard Frank, Personal 1975 (Box 38)
  - Public Relations, P/UD/I 1975-1978 (Box 38)
  - Kalamazoo Rotary Design Competition 1978 (Box 38)
  - Downriver Community Conference 1979 (Box 38)
  - General Correspondence
    - 1978 (Box 38)
    - 1979 (Box 38)
    - 1980 (Box 38)
  - Columbia University Lecture 1186-165 1980 (Box 38)
  - Frank Notebook 1981 (Box 38)
  - Design Workshop, "Historical Trends in Storefronts," Monroe 1980
    - Architectural Drawings, Visual Displays (Tube 19)
  - P/UD/I Notes, Buy/Sell 1981 (Box 39)
  - Tax Act Workshop, P/UD/I 1982 (Box 39)
  - Color Technology Notebook, P/UD/I 1982 (Box 39)
  - Preservation/Urban Design/Incorporated Brochure 1983-1984 (Box 39)
  - Black Book 1984 (Box 39)
  - Bob Marshall Operations 1984 (Box 39)
  - MMM International 1984 (Box 39)
  - MMM-P/UD/I Moves 1984 (Box 39)
  - MMM-P/UD/I Termination of Employment 1984 (Box 39)
  - McGaughy Memorandums 1984 (Box 39)
  - AIA Graphic Standards Task Group 1984-1987 (Box 39)
  - Architectural Registration, Michigan 1985-1987 (Box 39)
  - Midwest Archives Conference, Lansing 1989 (Box 39)
  - Shreve Weber Stellwagen, Engineering Board of Directors 1989-1993 (Box 39)
  - Friends of Kresge Presentation 1990 (Box 39)
  - Local History Conference, Detroit 1990 (Box 39)
  - Michigan Society of Planning Officials Training Workshop, Community Appearance 1994, 4 folders (Box 39)
  - Historical Preservation Building Code Seminar, Traverse City 1996 (Box 39)
  - Michigan Historic Preservation Network, Distinguished Service Award 1997 (Box 39)
- Visual Material